ongage.com 2017-01-12

# Privacy policy | Ongage

Ongage Ltd. is committed to your right to privacy. This privacy policy applies to information collected via Ongage internet website at www.ongageconnect.com (the “Site”), and/or the services available through the Site or otherwise provided by Ongage (the “Services”).  
The terms “Ongage”, “we”, “us”, “our” and “ours” when used in this Privacy Policy mean Ongage Ltd., which includes all its parents, subsidiaries, divisions, branches, and affiliates.  
The terms “you”, “your” and “yours” when used in this Privacy Policy means any user of the Site and/or Services.  
If you choose to register or submit information to the Site and Services, you agree to the use of such data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please note, that the Services may contain links to other sites maintained by third parties, which may not be governed by this privacy policy. Ongage is not responsible for the policies or practices of our customers or any third parties. You should review the applicable privacy policies of our customers and any third parties before providing them with any personally identifiable information.

 **1\. Ongage Best Practices & Anti-Spam Policy**

This policy applies to any and all electronic mail and/or other types of electronic messages or communications generated or sent through the services provided by Ongage (“Services”) whether through the site located at www.ongageconnect.com (the “Site”) or otherwise. Your use of the Site and/or Services is subject to this policy. If you are found to be in violation of this policy at any time, as determined by Ongage in its sole discretion, we may suspend or terminate your account. This Policy is a part of and is incorporated into the Ongage [Terms of Service](https://www.ongage.com/terms-of-service/ "Terms of Service").

DOS  
* You can only use Ongage Services to send emails to lists of people that gave you permission to email them. All email recipients must have opted in to, or otherwise validly consented to, receiving communications from you.  
* Your use of the Services must comply with all applicable laws, including laws relating to spam or unsolicited commercial email, privacy, security, obscenity, defamation, child protection, and other applicable laws. It is your responsibility to know and understand the laws applicable to your use of the Services.  
* Emails sent via the Services must contain an “unsubscribe” link that allows the recipients to remove themselves from your email messages. You must actively manage and process unsubscribe requests, and update your email lists and address books to reflect the unsubscribe requests.

DON’TS  
* You must not utilize the Services to send any commercial electronic mail messages (as defined in the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003) to any recipient who has opted out, unsubscribed, or otherwise objected to receiving such messages.  
* You must not utilize the Services to send messages to harvested mailing lists or to third-party, purchased, or rented mailing lists.  
* You must not send unsolicited mail to newsgroups, message boards, distribution lists, or email addresses.  
* You must not use the Services to send emails with deceptive subject lines or false or misleading header information.  
* You must not use the Services to send “junk mail”, “chain letters”, “pyramid schemes” or other materials that encourages recipients to forward the email to other recipients.

REPORT TO US

If you suspect that the Services have been used by someone to send spam, please contact us immediately at support@ongage.com and we will investigate the matter.  
If Ongage determines, in its sole discretion, that the email messages a user has sent via the Services generate a number of spam complaints in excess of industry standards, Ongage shall have the right to suspend or terminate its use of the Site and/or Services.

 **2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION**

We log visitor’s domain and IP address automatically; this information does not identify you as an individual, but only the computer that is being used to view the site. We also use cookies (small text files stored in a user’s browser) or Web beacons (electronic images that allow the website to count visitors who have accessed a particular page and to access certain cookies) to gather personally unidentified information. You may at any time program your browser to block cookies, but be aware that such blocking may prevent us from providing some or all of the Services to you.

Other than in respect of personally identified information, if you provide information to us, you agree that we have unlimited rights to such information and that we may use such information in any way we choose. Such information shall be deemed to be non-confidential.

Information that can identify a User (e.g. name or address) is not collected in this process. We collect only personally identified information that is specifically and voluntarily provided by you, for example, when you register for an account, we collect your username, password and email address. We may collect your personal information or data if you submit it to us in other contexts by using the Services, for example, your contact list, information you provide in structured profile fields or any content submitted, legal or financial details.. If you choose to register or submit information to the Site and/or Services, you agree to the use of such data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

 **3\. INFORMATION USE**

Non-personal information is used mainly for click stream analysis in order to constantly improve and maintain our Services, including among others, for ensuring the technical functioning of our network, to help prevent fraudulent use of our services and for developing new services.

Personal information is used only for limited purposes. For example, we may store user preferences, such as your default language or email account, to contact you in response to requests or inquiries, or to optimize the content we display and personalize your website experience. In addition, the web master may, where necessary, use your information for various site related tasks.

On occasion it is necessary to send out service related announcements. For instance, if the Sites or any of the Services is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. We also communicate with users to provide customer service in accordance with our Terms of Service. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications without also deactivating their account and ceasing use of the Services. These communications are not promotional in nature.

We may send new registrants of the Sites or Services a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members may occasionally also receive, if they so choose, information on special offers, products, services and periodic newsletters. Users may choose to opt-out and to not receive these communications.

Ongage may reach out to anyone who leaves their contacts details on our site, or through our call service, or with any employee or representative of Ongage. Ongage respects your privacy and we do not tolerate spam and will never sell, rent, lease or give away your information (name, address, email, etc.) to any third party. You can unsubscribe and opt-out from any communication from us at any time.

 **4\. SHARING OF INFORMATION**

We may share non-personal, aggregate information regarding site usage with our affiliates, partners and advertisers. From time to time, we may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in Ongage usage.

Ongage may share users’ information with the partners and service providers to facilitate the delivery of the Ongage Services and as necessary to allow you to enjoy the Services. Unless otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we do not share, sell, rent, or trade any personally identifiable information of our Users with third parties for their promotional commercial purposes. If you share your information using the Services with a third party’s website, please note that we do not control our business partners use of such information, and their use of the information will be in accordance with their own privacy policies.

Ongage IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE POLICIES OR PRACTICES OF OUR CUSTOMERS OR ANY THIRD PARTIES. YOU SHOULD REVIEW THE APPLICABLE PRIVACY POLICIES OF OUR CUSTOMERS AND ANY THIRD PARTIES BEFORE PROVIDING THEM WITH ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION.

 **5\. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER OF INFORMATION**

Ongage processes information on our servers in USA. To facilitate Ongage’s global Services, we may transfer and access information from around the world. For Users outside the U.S., please note that any information you share via the Services will be transferred out of your country and into the U.S. You consent to such transfer through your use of the Services. Ongage reserves the right to change its server locations to any location around the world.

 **6\. INFORMATION SECURITY**

We take appropriate security measures to protect Users’ information against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

 **7\. ACCESS TO INFORMATION**

We try to provide reasonable access to Users who wish to review the personal information retained via our Site and/or Services, and correct any inaccuracies it may contain. Users may independently access their user profile and account at any time, correct and update their details, or otherwise manage their account.

Ongage reserves the right to use or disclose personal information to law enforcement, regulatory or other government agencies, or third parties if we reasonably believe that use or disclosure is necessary to protect the Ongage’ rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or a legal process.

 **8\. MINOR’S PRIVACY PROTECTION**

Ongage understands the importance of protecting children’s privacy in the interactive online world. The Site and/or Services covered by this Privacy Policy are not designed for or intentionally targeted at children 13 years of age or younger. It is not our policy to intentionally collect, solicit or maintain information about anyone under the age of 13.

 **9\. ASSIGNMENT**

If Ongage elects, in its reasonable discretion, to transfer ownership or control of the Sites or Services to a third party, whether or not in the context of an acquisition, merger, or reorganization, you consent to the transfer of your personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information by Ongage to that third party, provided that all use of your information by that third party remains subject to the terms of this Policy.

 **10\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. You are encouraged to check and revisit this page as often as you wish to update yourself with any changes.

If you have any questions regarding this policy or do not feel that your concerns have been addressed, please direct your questions to: support@ongage.com.
